<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.4//EN"
"/usr/share/xml/docbook/schema/dtd/4.4/docbookx.dtd">
<book>
<bookinfo>
<title>ZFS Web Site</title>
</bookinfo>

<chapter><title>Landing Page</title>
<sect1><title>main body</title>
<para>
Knowledge Quest Infotech is proud to present the Technology Preview
(beta) of the ZFS* port to Linux. We are inviting participants for our
beta phase. If you are interested in our beta program please apply
here.

Why port ZFS to linux ? We believe that ZFS is a very innovative
filesystem which has taken a fresh and intuitive approach to storage
systems. Anyone who has used ZFS cannot deny being impressed by its
power and simplicity. We believe that ZFS should be available to a
larger Audience for use. And it is this belief that drives us to
deliver this port to linux.

Our port of ZFS is an extension to the port of DMU layer by Brian
Behlendorf. We have added the missing ZPL layer to Brian's port. With
this addition it becomes possible to mount the zfs filesystem on linux
and leverage ZFS's features on linux.

If you have any questions regarding this port please visit our FAQ. If
you want to contact us please drop us a mail at
zfs-query@kqinfotech.com

*ZFS is a trademark of Oracle.
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1><title>Our Approach</title>
<para>
It's in our DNA. Placing our clients first is embedded in the KQ
culture. By investing in our people and resources, we bring new ideas
and innovation to help you succeed in a changing business environment.
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1><title>Consulting Service</title>
<para>
KQ offers a variety of consulting servicesin the field of systems and
storage tailored to your needs. Leverage KQ's expertise in ZFS and
Systems programming by opting for consulting services. Click here to
know more about ZFS consulting services.
</para>
</sect1>

<sect1><title>KQ 2.0</title>
<para>
KQ 2.0 By employing the KQ 2.0 platform, we can bring the best people,
resources and capabilities of our global delivery system to any
client, anywhere
</para>
</sect1>
</chapter>


</book>